# **Pranav Rao**

I am an ambitious Computer Science Engineer. Looking for opportunities to use my skills for the betterment of the organization. I have been programming for more than two years and have developed my passion in Web Development and Software.

☑ pranavrao541@gmail.com

8080492106

in linkedin.com/in/pranav-rao-09a79b231

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Geopage Consultants | Bangalore**

Junior Frontend Developer

05/2024 - Present,

 Tech Stack: React.js, JavaScript, MUI, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap CSS, Node.js PostgreSQL, Basic DevOps

## AntStack Serverless Consulting Company | Bangalore

Frontend Web Developer Intern

11/2023 - 01/2024

• React.js, JavaScript, TypeScript, Tailwind CSS, Firebase, Supabase, Git

#### EDUCATION

#### Sharad Institute of Technology College of Engineering

B.Tech - 8.64 GPA 2023

## **Sanjay Bhokare Groups of Institute**

Diploma - 9.47 GPA 2020

#### **Alphonsa School Miraj**

SSC - 8.11 GPA 2017

#### PROJECT

#### **Personal Portfolio**

- · Tech Stack: Vite React, JavaScript, Tailwind CSS
- I have designed a portfolio. In the portfolio I have added all the necessary information about me.
- https://pranavrao-portfolio.vercel.app/

Instagram Clone 01/2024 - 03/2024

- Tech Stack: React, JavaScript. Chakra UI, Zustand
- Backend and Database Management: Firebase
- Functionalities: Create Account, (Create, Like, Comment, Delete) Post, etc.
- https://social-app-clone-jade-kappa.vercel.app/

Pollify 12/2023 - 01/2024

- · Tech Stack: React, JavaScript. Tailwind
- Backend and Database Management: Firebase
- Functionalities: Create Account, (Create, Edit, Delete) Polls, etc.
- https://pollify-sable.vercel.app/

#### SKILLS

 React, JavaScript, Typescript, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap CSS, CSS 3, HTML 5, Git, SQL, PostgreSQL, C/C++